Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - E, 1926, Elvey (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - F, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - G, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Ha-Hn, 1926, Harvard telegrams (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Ho-J, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - I-J, 1926, International Astronomical Union, Subcommittee of Commission 30 International Astronomical Union Justin (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - K, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - L, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Ma-Md, 1926, Mars, clippings (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Me-Mn, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Mo-N, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - N-Q, 1926, National Academy, 368 Helium Stars (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - R, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - R, 1926, Registering microphotometer Requests for circulars, catalogs (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Sn, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - So-Sz, 1926, Shapley Sullivan’s report on 40" dome and telescope (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - T-U, 1926, Telescopes, inquiries, sale University of Chicago Auditor (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago, accident H. M. Foote February 10, 1926 University of Chicago, Zabler accident May 15, 1926 University of Chicago, Parkhurst Residence Property, northeast boundary (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago, Dickerson and Moulds University of Chicago educational University of Chicago Graduate Office University of Chicago Graduate instruction (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Laboratory Supply, bills University of Chicago Library (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago University of Chicago President and Vice President (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago President’s Assistant, Henry J. Smith, Russell Pierce University of Chicago Press (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Press, 368 Helium Stars University of Chicago Publications Yerkes Observatory, stock on hand (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory V. IV pt. IV O.J. Lee, 1926 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory V. IV pt. V Farnsworth, 1926 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Recorder (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, building numbers University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, Mr. Foote’s estimates on repairs University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, monthly statement University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, supplies, engineers University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, supplies, gardeners (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - U, 1926, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, gravel and dust for driveways University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, Harold Foote University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, painting Bruce building University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, supplies, janitors University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, weight tickets, coal (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 3-4)
  - U-V, 1926, Visitors (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - W, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - X-Z, 1926, Report for Popular Astronomy, American Astronomical Society 1924-1925 Weather report material (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - A, 1927, American Astronomical Society meeting, Nashville American Astronomical Society (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - A-Bh, 1927, Applications for positions Barnard Atlas (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Bi-Bz, 1927, Bank deposits Berkeley telegrams Bibliographies (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - B-Ch, 1927, Bobrovnikoff Book announcements (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Ci-Cz, 1927, Carnegie Institution, Barnard Atlas (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - C-E, 1927, Copelin, Barnard Atlas (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - F, 1927 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Fecker, J. W., 1927 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - F-G, 1927, Frost, E. B., personal (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Ha-Hn, 1927, Harvard telegrams (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Ho-I, 1927, International Astronomical Union (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - I-K, 1927, International Astronomical Union Committee 3, American section (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - La-Md, 1927 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Astronomical inquiries from the public, 1927 (Box 113, Folder 5-6)
  - Me-Mz, 1927 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - N, 1927 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - O-P, 1927, Occultation of Saturn January 28, 1927 Press clippings (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Q-R, 1927, Requests for circulars and catalogs (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sn, 1927, Shapley (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - So-Sz, 1927, Sullivan’s reports on 40" dome (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - T-U, 1927, Telescopes, sale of and inquiries (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago accident reports University of Chicago Auditor (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Baker property University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Business Manager (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Cashier, Mather, A.J. University of Chicago Dickerson University of Chicago educational (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago fellowships and scholarships University of Chicago Gale-Michelson experiment (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago Graduate Office, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Graduate instruction University of Chicago great dome, steel wheels (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Laboratory Supply, bills University of Chicago Library (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago milling machine University of Chicago (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Photographic Supply Department, inquiries, but not orders, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago President, Vice President and Trustees, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Press, Barnard Atlas, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago, Barnard Atlas, publicity matters, 1927 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago publicity office, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory Vol. IV, pt 6, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory Vol. IV, pt 1 University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory, funds (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Recorder (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - U, 1927, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, Irvine property University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 6-7)
  - University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, 12 inch dome, alterations, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - V, 1927, Visitors (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - W-Z, 1927 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - W, 1927, Report of Yerkes Observatory 1926-1927 Weather report material (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Report of Yerkes Observatory for 1925-1927, 1927 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - A, 1928, Filing hints 1928 file (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - A-Bh, 1928, American Astronomical Society Applications for positions (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - B, 1928, Barnard Atlas Bank deposits (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Bi-Bz, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Ca-Ch, 1928 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Institution, correspondence, Barnard Atlas, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Calendar reform, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 2-3)
  - Ci-Cz, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - C-D, 1928, Copelin, Barnard Atlas (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - E, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - F, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Fecker, J.W., 1928 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - G, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - G-Hn, 1928, Gale, Henry, personal matters indirectly related to the University of Chicago (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Ho-I, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - International Astronomical Union, Committee 30, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - I-K, 1928, International Astronomical Union, Committee 30 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - L, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Ma-Mh, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Mi-Mz, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Astronomical inquiries from the public, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago, 1928 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - N, 1928, Naval Observatory, sunspot data (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - N-O, 1928, Naval Observatory, photographic equipment (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - P-R, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Requests for pamphlets and catalogs (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Sa-Sn, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Shapley, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - So-Sz, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - T-U, 1928 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Auditor, 1928 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Business Manager (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Cashier University of Chicago correcting lens for 40" University of Chicago Dickerson (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago educational University of Chicago fellowships and scholarships University of Chicago graduate instruction (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Graduate Office University of Chicago Laboratory supplies University of Chicago Library (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago, Photographic Supply Department inquiries but not orders University of Chicago President, Vice-President, and Trustees (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago bibliography, O. Struve University of Chicago Press, Boyer, Beam and Press (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Press McFarland University of Chicago Press, correspondence, Barnard Atlas (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Press, exchanges with Astrophysical Journal University of Chicago Publicity Office University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory, Vol 4 pt. 7 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory, Vol 4 pt. 7 University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory, Funds University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory, Vol 6 pt. 1 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Recorder University of Chicago, changes in toilet rooms (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago secretary, 1928 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, 1928 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago, Superintendent of construction, 1928 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, new construction, L. R. Flook University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, Eckart Laboratory (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, orders and numbers University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, repairs at Director’s garage (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - U, 1928, University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - U-V, 1928 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Visitors, 1928 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - X-Z, 1928, YMCA Golf Club Sullivan report on 40" dome Yerkes Observatory report for Popular Astronomy, 1927- 1928 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - A, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - A, 1929, American Astronomical Society Applications for positions (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Ba-Bh, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Bi-Bz, 1929, Bank deposits (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Ca-Ch, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Calendar reform, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Calendar reform, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Bi-Cz, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - D-E, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - F, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - F, 1929, Fecker, J.W. Fireballs, July 25, November 5 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - G, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Ha-Hn, 1929, Henry Gale (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Ho-I, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - I-J, 1929, International Astronomical Union (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - K-Lh, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Li-Ml, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Mi-Mz, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - N, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Naval Observatory, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - O-P, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Photoelectric Photometer, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Q-R, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Requests for pamphlets and catalogs, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Sa-Sn, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - S, 1929, Shapley (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Spectrohelioscope, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - T-U, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Auditor, now called comptroller, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Auditor, statements and petty, request 43589, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, July-December, 1929 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago, building numbers University of Chicago, houses 7, 8, 9 University of Chicago, water and sewage in Williams Bay (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago, coal University of Chicago, electric bills University of Chicago, mowing bills (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago Business Manager, Vice President, and Real Estate Manager Lesch University of Chicago Cashier (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago Dickerson University of Chicago fellowships University of Chicago graduate instructions, graduate students coming to Yerkes (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Graduate Office, 1929 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Library, 1929 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago University of Chicago Photographic Supply Department, inquiries (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago President’s Office, 1929 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago Press, lecture, 24 slides University of Chicago Press, Bean (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Press, Laing, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Bookstore, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago Publicity Office University of Chicago Publications, Yerkes Observatory, includes Barnard’s clusters, 500 stars (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - U, 1929, University of Chicago Recorder University of Chicago Secretary (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - V-W, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Visitors, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Weather report, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - X-Z, 1929, Yerkes staff reports Sullivan’s reports on the big dome Popular Astronomy YMCA letters (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - A, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - American Astronomical Society, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Applications for positions, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Ba-Bh, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Bi- Bz, 1930, Bank deposits (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Ca-Ch, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Ci-Cz, 1930, Snowy tree cricket (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - D, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - E, 1930, Eclipse, August 31, 1932 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Ernostar lenses, 1930 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - F, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - G, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - H, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - I-J, 1930, International Astronomical Union (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - K, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - L, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Ma-Mi, 1930, Conjunctions Mercury and Venus, April 22-27 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Mi-Mz, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - N, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Naval Observatory, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - O-P, 1930 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - P-R, 1930, Photoelectric Photometer (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Requests for pamphlets and catalogs, 1930 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Sn, 1930, Shapley (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - So-Sz, 1930 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Spectroheliograph, new, 1930 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - T-U, 1930, University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, 1930 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, new acquisitions, 1930 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, building numbers University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, bids for work to be done at Yerkes Observatory University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, houses, 7, 8, 9, 9 (2), 10 University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, coal bills University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, electric bills (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills University of Chicago, Business Manager University of Chicago, Cashier (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago, Comptroller University of Chicago, Comptroller, petty cash and statements (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago, educational University of Chicago, fellowships University of Chicago, graduate instruction (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Graduate Office, 1930 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago Library University of Chicago (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago President University of Chicago Vice President F. Woodward (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1930 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago Press, Bean University of Chicago Press, Hemens University of Chicago Press, McFarland University of Chicago Press, Laing University of Chicago Press, Manning, Ryan University of Chicago Press, Bookstore University of Chicago Publicity Office (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - U, 1930, University of Chicago Purchasing Department University of Chicago Recorder University of Chicago Secretary (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - V-W, 1930 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Visitors, 1930 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - X-Z, 1930, Weather reports (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - X-Z, 1930, Zabler compensation for broken arm Yerkes Observatory staff reports For Popular Astronomy YMCA, Walworth County (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - A, 1931 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - A, 1931, American Astronomical Society Applications for positions (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Ba-Bh, 1931 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Bi-Bz, 1931, Bank deposits Belopololsky 1921-1931 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Ca-Ch, 1931, Calendar reform (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Ci-Cz, 1931, Chicago Worlds Fair, "Century of Progress" (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - D-E, 1931 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - F-G, 1931 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - H-J, 1931, International Astronomical Union (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - K-L, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Ma-Mh, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Mi-Mz, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - N, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - N-P, 1931, Naval Observatory (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - R, 1931, Requests for lantern slide catalogs (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - S, 1931, Shapley (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - S-U, 1931, Smith, Secaucus New Jersey, Cosmic Ray Swindle Sullivan’s report (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1931 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills, 1931 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bids for work at Yerkes University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, building numbers University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric light bills (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago, Buildings and Grounds, houses 8, 9, 9 (2), 10 University of Chicago Bookstore (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago Cashier University of Chicago Comptroller (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago Comptroller, petty statements University of Chicago fellowships University of Chicago Graduate Office (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Dean Gale, Divisional Dean, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago graduate students reports University of Chicago Library University of Chicago (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago President’s Office University of Chicago Press (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - U, 1931, University of Chicago Publications of Yerkes Observatory University of Chicago Press, McFarland University of Chicago Press, Crane University of Chicago Publicity Office (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Department, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Recorder, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Secretary, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Vice President, 1931 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - U-V, 1931 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - W, 1931, Weather Bureau and reports Visitors (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - X-Z, 1931, Yerkes Observatory staff reports YMCA (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - A, 1932, Acme Aluminum Foundry Co., 1 page Adams, W.S. (Mount Wilson), 5 pages Addey, T, 1 page Agfa Ansco Corporation, 5 pages Agnesia, Sr. M., 1 page Aitken, R. G. (Lick Observatory), 9 pages Albaugh-Dover, 2 pages Albrecht, Sebastian (Dudley), 5 pages Almer Coe and Company, 2 pages Alumaweld Company, 2 pages Aluminum Company of America, 1 page American Askania Corporation, 2 pages American Association for the Advancement of Science, 8 pages American Blower Corporation, 3 pages American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 3 pages Amkniga Corporation, 2 pages Amlie, Thomas (Congressman), 7 pages Anderson, George, 2 pages Anderson, J. A. (Mount Wilson), 3 pages Armenter, F, 2 pages Armstrong, J. R., 3 pages Ashley, Moses M. (Nadir-Zenith Astronomy Committee), 3 pages Astronomical Society Pacific (C. A. Adams, Secretary), 6 pages Astronomische Nachrichten, (H. Kobold, editor), 2 pages Atlantic Photogesellschaft, 3 pages Hotel Austin, 1 page (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - B, 1932, Baade, W. (Mount Wilson), 1 page Badger Foundry, 8 pages Barrett, S. B., 3 pages Bartky, W., 1 page Barton, S. G. (University of Pennsylvania), 3 pages Bauer, Fred J., 2 pages Bausch and Lomb, 11 pages Beck, Charlton T. (University of Chicago Magazine), 1 page Beckwith, Mrs. W. E., 2 pages Bedell, Ralph C., 1 page Beer, Arthur, 3 pages Bell Labs (C. E. Bisdee), 2 pages Beloit Daily News, 2 pages Charles H. Besley and Company, 2 pages James G Biddle Company, 1 page Birge, Raymond T., 2 pages Blair, L. F., 1 page Bobrovnikoff, N. T. (Perkins), 1 page Bodine Electric Company, 19 pages Boss, Benjamin (Dudley), 1 page Boston Gear Works, 9 pages Bowditch, Ingersoll, 1 page Bowman, Gwendolyn, 2 pages Brandi-Silva, 1 page Brentano’s, 2 pages Brown, William H., 2 pages Brown Paper Company, 3 pages Brown, E. W. (Yale) for International Astronomical Union, 2 pages Buchhandlung Gustav Fock, 1 page Buckles, Harold, 1 page Budd Grate Company, 1 page Burlington Brass Foundry, 11 pages Burnham, Harold C., 6 pages (Box 138, Folder 6)